A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Tsubaki and Blackstar have been sent to the village of Shin to hunt the Enchanted Sword,
a weapon who teeters on the brink of becoming a Kishin.
The Enchanted Sword possesses whoever wields it,
taking over their body, controlling their shadow, and eventually devouring their soul.
There is a reason why this pair, who have yet to collect a single Kishin soul,
were sent to complete such a dangerous and deadly mission.
Tsubaki.
Hi, brother.
Tsubaki is the only one who can defeat the Enchanted Sword.
Thank you.
Zubaki.
Did you hear me?
I said get out!
Get out!
Okay.
Just make sure you come back.
Zubaki, the Camellia Blossom.
What lies beyond the grief?
You're powerless.
What's the matter, Zubaki?
I know you didn't come just to visit, so why aren't you attacking?
You're just like your namesake, the Camellia Blossom.
A flower without fragrance.
It proclaims nothing but blooms in pathetic silence.
When your petals scatter, it is quietly tragic.
Such a boring flower.
Do you know what I think?
I think if this was the outside world, you'd be dead by now.
What's the matter?
Your soul's trembling.
What do you fear?
Is it death?
I may die today, but I will stop you.
Don't look at me.
Stop it.
Those eyes.
It was you.
You're the one who led me here.
You brought me to the path of the Enchanted Sword.
Get out!
Blackstar showing more restraint with those two than I thought was possible for him.
I can't believe Zubaki and the Sword are brother and sister.
But Blackstar still has no idea about that, does he?
Mm-hmm.
He trusts her.
And for now, that's all he needs to know.
Zubaki isn't moving.
Are you sure she's all right?
What's she doing in there anyway?
Hmm.
Well, you see, it's like this.
Hmm?
We brought snacks, everybody!
Snacks at a time like this?
What are you two different thinking?
Let's see, how should I put this?
To describe it simply, Zubaki is engaged in a sort of soul tug-of-war with the Enchanted Sword, Masamune.
As her brother makes his move to possess her soul, Zubaki is countering by trying to absorb his.
The struggle will continue until one soul defeats the other and wins.
Zubaki's using his own technique against him. Nice.
But do you think she has any chance of winning?
It will be difficult for her.
It's the sword's soul, so he's got home court advantage.
And soul possession is one of his trademark techniques.
Yeah.
Altogether, the chance that Zubaki will win is low.
Brother and sister locked in a fight to the death! I can't even imagine it!
I couldn't go on living without you, Patty!
We're there.
A person who chooses the path of the Kishin reveals his own weakness.
The original Kishin sought power in order to escape the fear of death.
Why has Zubaki's brother chosen this path to power?
What does he seek to gain by becoming a Kishin?
You have so many other options.
You could use your smoke bomb or shuriken.
But you stick with your plain Okasarigama.
Why are you holding back?
Pity?
Do you pity me?
Zubaki and Masamune both come from the Nakatsukasa family.
That clan possesses special weapon abilities that are handed down through the generations.
The previous generation's abilities should have been passed down to Masamune as he was the eldest son.
But instead...
You inherited everything that should have gone to me by birthright.
I inherited only one thing.
This sword.
For some reason, the power was given to Zubaki.
As a child, I was treated more delicately than other boys.
I was babied for so long.
I got whatever I asked for, but I never realized it was because I was inferior.
In the end, the one who showed me that sad truth was you.
The pity in your eyes. That's how you looked at me when we were children, when you hid your own emotions because you thought you were the strong one.
I'll never forgive you for that.
Zubaki, dear sister, I'm going to kill you.
I will become a Kishin.
And then...
I will master this sword.
Puppet Rain.
Black star.
Star.
Zubaki.
Remember our entrance ceremony at the Academy? The incredible performance I gave? I remember it perfectly.
Yahoo!
Fellow students, remember this well! I am Blackstar, the world's greatest assassin! The big man! I will transcend death!
Is that a jumper?
Or an idiot?
Or an escaped lunatic.
Try not to feel too bad about living in my shadow!
It isn't your fault that I'm the biggest star ever!
Sooner or later you will all cower before me!
Let me hear you now! Scream the name of Blackstar!
Huh. It looks like this world might not be ready for me.
Be ready for me!
Wow! That was amazing!
Yeah?
You're the first person to appreciate my talent. Good for you. You'll go far. Now, what's your name?
What's your name?
Oh, Zubaki. I'm a weapon.
I'm the world's greatest assassin, Blackstar!
I'm a Meister.
That was the first time we met. You watched my performance all the way through to the end that day.
Now it's my turn to see you all the way through.
Who's this woman? She's been sitting there for a long time.
You're with him, aren't you? Well, you can get out of our village, too!
Listen, you little brat.
Don't even think about interrupting Zubaki again or I'll kill you!
You got me.
Just sit there and keep your mouth shut.
Oh, yeah! We'll spook you, StarClan!
Do you have any last words before I kill you?
You truly are a pathetic little Camellia Blossom, aren't you? Nothing to say.
Hey, Zubaki, what do you feel like playing today?
Whatever you want to!
Come on, Zubaki!
You always want to play my game. What do you want to play?
Okay...
I want to play ball!
And now, Zubaki, your soul belongs to me.
What's Zubaki thinking, taking him on all alone?
Zubaki is a powerful, adaptable weapon. She's very good at what she does, but this time her opponent is too strong.
I should have been the one to face the Enchanted Sword.
But she's not really alone.
Blackstar is sitting right next to her, and he won't budge.
Zubaki wouldn't be able to fight if he wasn't there with her, would she?
Right! What's important now is what's in here.
We all know Zubaki is an incredibly versatile weapon.
She has many modes of attack to defeat her, and she's not able to fight her.
And she's not really alone.
But that's not where her true strength lies.
She carries that in her soul.
Watch closely this time, okay?
Okay.
See?
Oh!
Did you really want to play ball, Zubaki?
Yes!
But I didn't.
What I really wanted to do was play house.
I wonder how long we could have played together if I'd been able to tell him that.
I am Zubaki, a flower without fragrance.
And when I fall, it will be silent and tragic.
What are you feeling right now, little sister?
Do you still look down on me?
It must be nice to have such a sense of superiority over others.
You just stand there quiet and smug, taking care of everyone else because you're the strong one.
How can you deny it?
That's who you've always been.
Oh!
Please tell me that's not what you're actually thinking.
You know better than that, Zubaki.
Don't even listen to this guy.
You're wrong!
I won't take care of you anymore!
That's over!
I'm going to stop you!
Please, feel in your soul how serious I am!
I'm begging you!
You're wrong!
Please feel in your soul how serious I am. I'm begging you
You don't stand a chance no matter how brave you pretend to be you're still just a pathetic flower with no voice or fragrance
You're wrong. I won't let you call me a pathetic flower
I have a friend who's helped me realize something. He's helped me see that a camellia
Does have a fragrance
Oh
It's a buggy
She's going inside the enchanted sword
No, that can't be right
Did he beat Tsubaki?
Does that mean it's over?
Tsubaki
I won't watch this. It can't be real
Oh, dude, let me have that stare
Hey Tsubaki come out of there already. You haven't lost to him. Have you you can put on a better show than that come back out on stage
Encore encore
Tsubaki encore give us an encore
At last you finally shown me what your feelings really are
I
I thought the camellia blossom was a boring flower one without any fragrance
But I was wrong wasn't I as soon as I touched your soul. I realized that
It's a nice fragrance
It took her away
Is it?
Why is it gonna be crazy?
The rain is still in the forest
Encore, Encore, Encore, Encore, Encore, Encore, Encore, come on Encore, Encore damn it, give us an Encore, we want an Encore
See I came back
Zubaki
I just had to pay a visit to my brother
You did huh, welcome back, are you all right? I'm fine
Are you sure you're really okay? Yes, I promise I'm okay
All right then come here come over here Blackstar is giving you a big hug
I'm sorry
Look at you Blackstar, you're all covered in blood, are you all right?
Never mind about me Zubaki, I'm fine
That's it you little
Real cool
Kid still alive then? That's good news
The StarClan are all monsters beating a little kid
Get out of here, now!
You ever notice how little dogs always feel the need to bark loud?
Why don't you much shut up?
You're scared of an enemy that doesn't exist anymore
How lame are you?
What's the point of worrying about the past?
A real star always keeps moving forward
Don't give us that
Who wants to come back here anyway?
I'm sorry, once you get to know him, he's not bad, really
Even if he wasn't a member of the Star Clan, I still wouldn't like that guy
So, Tsubaki, now that we're done with the enchanted sword
And you've taken care of some baggage from your past
You're still gonna be my weapon, right?
Of course
All right
Hey guys, welcome back
Thanks, what did we miss?
I'm sorry we made you all worry
Hey, hey, good work, you two
Yeah, you guys were amazing out there
And you finally bagged a soul, huh?
The problem child finally redeems himself
It sure took you long enough, though
I've always been a little bit ahead of my time
You did it, Tsubaki
That little baby cried, you know
Nuh-uh, that was you, sis
You know, Lord Death
I think I may have underestimated what those kids were capable of
They're not so bad
They are still young, after all
They've got plenty of growing up left to do
Attention
I hope you're all ready
Because you're about to see something incredibly awesome
Oh, this should be good
Okay, listen to this
Thanks to that soul we bagged, Tsubaki's got a brand new mode
Let's show him, Tsubaki
Great
Enchanted thorn mode, let's go
Oh
Ah
My soul wavelength just got taken away
I'm gonna miss it
I don't think that's what Blackstar had planned
He might not be ready for that yet
This is interesting, though
Looks like Tsubaki inherited her brother's power
Ah
This settles it
I was born way too soon
The times are never able to keep up with me
Then we'll wait for them together
Right, Blackstar?
I want to be
Kiera meku
Yume no
Hoshi sa
I wanna be
I koze
I wanna be an Pues que your world is green
吐く息は白いままなのに
今を分壊しに行こうって約束した
あの日からきっとまだ間に合うはずだから
I wanna be less so on that
We'll be right back.
I'm so glad that story had a happy ending.
Thanks, Maka.
You can have it too, you know.
Have what, Tsubaki?
Happiness, of course.
In other words, this right here.
A jar?
With this jar, anyone can find true happiness.
Order today and I'll throw in a second one free.
Take advantage of this limited time offer
while you've still got the chance.
Uh, Tsubaki?
On the next episode of Soul Eater,
Courage That Beats Out Fear,
Maka Albarn's Great Resolution?
Watch it, or I'll take your soul.
Order quickly while supplies last.
On the next episode of Soul Eater,
h Teres and I'llimein.
In the next episode of Soul Eandam's Great Resolution,
축ート, Truth in the World,
society has a short time opportunity,
and will they do nothing with this overlap and
take care of themselves.
So here, your heart is у Sila,
andcja is the plan for him.
If there are comparators at the other,
it will be the case that comes with that.